        The polar graph displayed it’s a representation of the v x B vector, projected to the North-South polarization direction [8.b], as function of azimuth for different zenith angles, color coded by amplitude.
        For the location of the Pierre Auger Observatory (B-field azimuth  = 90 degrees, zenith = 54 degrees), the North-South polarization channel has maximum amplitudes recorded from East and West arrival direction of air showers, moreover for higher zenith angles (above 60 degrees), and minimum amplitudes for showers coming from North and South directions.
